[Music]
insurance we protect our cars our homes
the things we value simple but what
about life
insurance seems complicated right it
doesn't have to be simply put life
insurance is about providing financial
protection for the people you care about
whether you're making sure your
beneficiaries can manage debt or the
cost of living or if you want to leave
them with a lasting Financial Legacy the
life insurance coverage can help provide
options for those you care about most by
giving them
choices there are two types of life
insurance term and
permanent term insurance is temporary
you buy it for a set period of time 10
or 20 years to ensure your beneficiaries
aren't burdened with financial
obligations like ongoing living expenses
or a mortgage term insurance is often
very affordable but remember once the
term ends so does your protection
permanent Insurance like whole life or
universal life is well permanent it
stays with you for life allowing you to
leave a financial Legacy for the people
you care about while it can be more
expensive than term insurance permanent
Insurance features investment
opportunities that can allow the value
of your policy to grow over time
potentially increasing the worth of your
estate term permanent both your adviser
can help you go beyond the basics and
create an insurance plan that can really
help protect the people you care about